<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Candy R. Boatwright</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Candy R. Boatwright</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Poinsett Bridge...and AI</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/poinsettbridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/poinsettbridge/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/image.png&#34; alt=&#34;Poinsett Bridge&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Poinsett Bridge in the upper part of Greenville County, South Carolina&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s all I typed&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;All that follows was autopopulated from just those 12 words&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;AUTO-GENERATED BY AI &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip;is the oldest bridge in South Carolina. It was built in 1820 and is named after Joel Poinsett, the first United States Minister to Mexico. The bridge includes a 14-foot Gothic arch and stretches 130 feet over Little Gap Creek. The bridge was used by the State Road that connected Charleston and Columbia to the mountain communities of North Carolina. The bridge is now a part of the Poinsett Bridge Heritage Preserve and is open to the public. The bridge is a popular spot for photographers and hikers. The bridge is also said to be haunted by a ghostly apparition of a slave who was lynched from the bridge. The bridge is a popular spot for photographers and hikers. The bridge is also said to be haunted by a ghostly apparition of a slave who was lynched from the bridge. The bridge is a popular spot for photographers and hikers. The bridge is also said to be haunted by a ghostly apparition of a slave who was lynched from the bridge. The bridge is a popular spot for photographers and hikers. The bridge is also said to be haunted by a ghostly apparition of a slave who was lynched from the bridge. The bridge is a popular spot for photographers and hikers. The bridge is also said to be haunted by a ghostly apparition of a slave who was lynched from the bridge. The bridge is a popular spot for photographers and hikers. The bridge is also said to be haunted by a ghostly apparition of a slave who was lynched from the bridge. The bridge is a popular spot for photographers and hikers. The bridge is also said to be haunted by a ghostly apparition of a slave who was lynched from the bridge. The bridge is a popular spot for photographers and hikers. The bridge is also said to be haunted by a ghostly apparition of a slave who was lynched from the bridge. The bridge is a popular spot for photographers and hikers. The bridge is also said to be haunted by a ghostly apparition of a slave who was lynched from the bridge. The bridge is a popular spot for photographers and hikers. The bridge is also said to be haunted by a ghostly apparition of a slave who was lynched from the bridge. The bridge is a popular spot for photographers and hikers. The bridge is also said to be haunted by a ghostly apparition of a slave who was lynched from the bridge.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring HTML, CSS, and H-Net</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/exploringhtmlcssandhnet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/exploringhtmlcssandhnet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;September 21, 2022&#xA;Exploring HTML, CSS and H-Net&#xA;We had the opportunity to learn about and do some hands-on exercises with HTML and CSS in my Digital Methods class this week. We started with HTML in Codeacademy and I was amazed how quickly those concepts gelled. I think that it took us all longer to access the tutorial than it did getting the hang of the commands. Also, I have also never been so thankful to have taken a Java class in high school and could still hear my sweet teacher’s voice in my head…”Did you remember to close that section?”.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thinking About Chalk</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/thinkingaboutchalk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/thinkingaboutchalk/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My grandfather was a high school history teacher. He had to write with chalk…Promethean boards didn’t exist. I don’t remember this personally because he had retired by the time I was a kid, but my mom used to tell me that his hands would get so dry from using the chalk that they would crack and bleed. Sometimes during class. So, here’s my grandfather, the kindest and most patient man I have ever met, bleeding in order to make it possible for his students to copy down notes and be better informed human beings.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
