<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homepage on Candy R. Boatwright</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homepage on Candy R. Boatwright</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Poinsett Bridge...and AI</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/poinsettbridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/poinsettbridge/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/PoinsettBridge.png&#34; alt=&#34;Poinsett Bridge&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Poinsett Bridge in the upper part of Greenville County, South Carolina&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s all I typed&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;All that follows was autopopulated from just those 12 words&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;AUTO-GENERATED BY AI &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip;is the oldest bridge in South Carolina. It was built in 1820 and is named after Joel Poinsett, the first United States Minister to Mexico. The bridge includes a 14-foot Gothic arch and stretches 130 feet over Little Gap Creek. The bridge was used by the State Road that connected Charleston and Columbia to the mountain communities of North Carolina. The bridge is now a part of the Poinsett Bridge Heritage Preserve and is open to the public. The bridge is a popular spot for photographers and hikers. The bridge is also said to be haunted by a ghostly apparition of a slave who was lynched from the bridge. The bridge is a popular spot for photographers and hikers. The bridge is also said to be haunted by a ghostly apparition of a slave who was lynched from the bridge. The bridge is a popular spot for photographers and hikers. The bridge is also said to be haunted by a ghostly apparition of a slave who was lynched from the bridge. The bridge is a popular spot for photographers and hikers. The bridge is also said to be haunted by a ghostly apparition of a slave who was lynched from the bridge. The bridge is a popular spot for photographers and hikers. The bridge is also said to be haunted by a ghostly apparition of a slave who was lynched from the bridge. The bridge is a popular spot for photographers and hikers. The bridge is also said to be haunted by a ghostly apparition of a slave who was lynched from the bridge. The bridge is a popular spot for photographers and hikers. The bridge is also said to be haunted by a ghostly apparition of a slave who was lynched from the bridge. The bridge is a popular spot for photographers and hikers. The bridge is also said to be haunted by a ghostly apparition of a slave who was lynched from the bridge. The bridge is a popular spot for photographers and hikers. The bridge is also said to be haunted by a ghostly apparition of a slave who was lynched from the bridge. The bridge is a popular spot for photographers and hikers. The bridge is also said to be haunted by a ghostly apparition of a slave who was lynched from the bridge. The bridge is a popular spot for photographers and hikers. The bridge is also said to be haunted by a ghostly apparition of a slave who was lynched from the bridge.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Song</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/hurricanesong/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/hurricanesong/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I stepped out onto my back porch around 10:00 to watch the wind and rain continue to billow as Hurricane Helene moved through my area in the Upstate of South Carolina. We lost electricity around 6:30 that morning, but I had the coffee made so it didn’t feel desperate. Then the phone and therefore browsing service got spotty and eventually disappeared. Desperate is a relative term. One of our trees had fallen onto our fence and into our neighbors yard and I dreaded assessing the damage. My dad was out of town leaving my mom at their house on her own. I worried about the water rising on their property. I wondered how much longer the charges on our phones would last. I couldn’t get on the power company’s website to see if there was an estimated restoration time. Were our relatives in Georgia doing alright? Had my friend Sally’s trees near her house come down in the wind? Was the playdate my daughter had planned with her soccer teammates for this afternoon going to be able to happen? What if power didn’t come back on for days? How long does food last in a freezer without electricity? What about the research I had planned for the day? What about the assignments I had due? Why hadn’t I ordered more of the books I needed to read for my classes? Why hadn’t I made the kids shower last night? Were any of my texts even getting through?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accomplishment</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/accomplishment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/accomplishment/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Between my life as a student and a mother I rarely, if ever, lay my head on the pillow at night feeling that I have accomplished everything I should have that day. It doesn’t matter that my assignments are done and my children are clean and fed and my house is fairly tidy. It doesn’t matter if I’ve spent time talking to my mom or my grandmother. It doesn’t matter if my husband and I spent time actually looking at each other’s faces and hanging out. It doesn’t matter what I have done, I almost always dwell on all the things I have yet to do.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSI: Greenville</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/portfolio/csigreenville/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/portfolio/csigreenville/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This was created as the final project for the &amp;ldquo;Digital Methods II&amp;rdquo; course at Clemson University. By examining the CSI:Dixie dataset created at the University of Georgia and focusing on the data available for South Carolina, patterns of regionality emerge. Cororners inquest documents form the basis of this dataset and provide not only information about the causes of death prevelant during the 19th century, but also the correlation between government policies and public health.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joseph McCullough House</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/josephmcculloughhouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/josephmcculloughhouse/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/McCulloughHouse.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Painting of the Joseph McCullough House&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In Elise Lathrop’s 1926 book, Early American Inns and Taverns, she states that there were not many old inns in South Carolina. She defines ‘old’ as at least 100 years old from the time of her writing. She mentions a few old inns, sometimes called ‘ordinaries’ in the south, in and around Charleston, but only one in the upstate of South Carolina. It was on the stagecoach road than ran from Greenville, SC to Augusta, GA.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where the sidewalk ends</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/digitaltoolswebsite/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/digitaltoolswebsite/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Well, this is it! The culmination of the work that I’ve done this semester in my Digital Methods class at Clemson. If you had told me going into this class that I would build not one, but two WordPress sites I wouldn’t have believed you. And really, building the WordPress sites was a sidenote to all of the technology we were introduced to and had the opportunity to work with!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The final countdown...20 seconds on repeat</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/finalproject/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/finalproject/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Below you will find my Pecha Kucha project which serves as the presentation portion of my final project for Digital Methods. Wish me luck!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;text-align: center; margin-top: 20px;&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/files/HIST8500-Pecha-Kucha.pptx&#34; download style=&#34;text-decoration: none;&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;button style=&#34;background-color: #007BFF; color: white; border: none; padding: 10px 20px; font-size: 16px; border-radius: 5px; cursor: pointer;&#34;&gt;&#xA;      Download Pecha Kucha Slideshow&#xA;    &lt;/button&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tableau...maybe not as simple as it appears?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/tableau/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/tableau/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I got super excited about Tableau during our class with Matt Chambers who is a RCID PhD student here at Clemson. It may have had a little to do with the Tableau visualization that he created for the play-by-play Clemson v Alabama 2017 National Championship game that ended with the forever enshrined Philippians 4:13 pass. But I was also excited about the incredibly rich and varied visualization possibilities available with Tableau. Now, I had done the class reading and understood that data preparation was key to correct visualizations in Tableau. I heard Matt say that getting the data into the correct format for Tableau to read was probably one of the most difficult steps of the process. But was I deterred from jumping in with both feet and creating my own dataset to try and predict who the winner of Season 10 of The Great British Baking Show was going to be on the Friday following our Wednesday Tableau class? No! I was not!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palladio</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/palladio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/palladio/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Palladio has a similar feel to Voyant as a “plug and play” web-based tool. It’s dashboard is so simple that initially it feels like you might have missed a step in the instructions. But, once you start exploring some of it’s capabilities and looking at projects in which its utilized it’s really an impressive digital research tool.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The first step is to upload your database. We used a Excel spreadsheet that contains two columns: author name and keyword. The spreadsheet was created by our Digital History instructor, Dr. Seefeldt, for a Buffalo Bill project he worked on.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voyant</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/voyant/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/voyant/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I chose to use Jacob Taubes’ Occidental Eschatology as my corpus in Voyant. Because the only version I had was a PDF of a photocopy of the book, the first time I uploaded it Voyant wasn’t able to recognize any of the text. I ran it through Adobe’s OCR feature and uploaded that and most of the text became readable for Voyant. The image below shows the first word cloud that was generated for the text after performing OCR.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ArcGIS StoryMaps</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/storymaps/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/storymaps/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p style=&#34;font-size: 18px; font-weight: bold;&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &#34;StoryMaps: The Family-Friendly Solution to Tedious Historical Narratives&#34;&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;text-align: center; margin-top: 24px;&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;a href=&#34;https://arcg.is/1PGvbn1&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; style=&#34;text-decoration: none;&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;button style=&#34;background-color: #522D80; color: white; border: none; padding: 10px 20px; font-size: 16px; border-radius: 5px; cursor: pointer;&#34;&gt;&#xA;      Check out my Seussian StoryMap&#xA;    &lt;/button&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Last week after doing the reading about StoryMaps for my Digital History class I wrote in my reflection that I was interested in learning more about other platforms that would be able to handle more complex narratives in a digital space. I would like to say that I stand well and truly corrected. For some reason (lets just blame it on sleep deprivation, shall we?) I was remembering StoryMaps from the summer GIS workshop I attended as only able to produce very simple online maps with narrative overlay and, boy, do I feel silly now!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airtables for Census Data</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/airtables/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/airtables/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If nothing else, beginning to trying and use Airtables for census data convinced me of the absolute necessity for collaboration across multiple academic fields as history scholars. I might be good at looking at census data and understanding the narrative I’m trying to tell with the information I’m seeing, but ask me to map out a database system to create a working digital model of the data and I am in the weeds.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omeka S</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/omekas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/omekas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Omeka S is an open-source platform that allows users to create a digital exhibit on the front end and populate the individual items’ back-end with metadata that allows the exhibit to connect with other online resources and researchers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We installed Omeka through our Reclaim Hosting site and then selected three images of a Clemson University building/space along with supporting materials from The Tiger (Clemson’s newspaper), TAPS (Clemson’s yearbook) and Board of Trustee’s minutes. I received an error message while loading my first images. Once I entered “/usr/bin” into the ImageMagick Directory Path in Settings my images and their thumbnails loaded correctly.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/tropy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/tropy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Tropy is a desktop application developed by a group of faculty and students at George Mason University (the same group that created Zotero which I reviewed in a previous blog post). It is designed to allow users to save, organize, and mark-up images of primary source research materials. It is a beautifully simple and amazingly intuitive system. I found the tagging feature to be especially helpful because it is so customizable to your specific project as well as your personal research style. The video below is a quick demo of the filter by tag function.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zotero...it&#39;s magic!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/zotero2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/zotero2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I believe that the inscription above the entrance to every college and university History Department should be sandblasted and replaced with ‘Zotero – Citations Simplified’. I mean, seriously, in one thousand years when our ancestors are trying to piece together the remnants of our digital age I, for one, would love for them to know that whatever mistakes we made, we at least figured out how to automate citing secondary source materials in our historical research papers.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring HTML, CSS, and H-Net</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/exploringhtmlcssandhnet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/exploringhtmlcssandhnet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;September 21, 2022&#xA;Exploring HTML, CSS and H-Net&#xA;We had the opportunity to learn about and do some hands-on exercises with HTML and CSS in my Digital Methods class this week. We started with HTML in Codeacademy and I was amazed how quickly those concepts gelled. I think that it took us all longer to access the tutorial than it did getting the hang of the commands. Also, I have also never been so thankful to have taken a Java class in high school and could still hear my sweet teacher’s voice in my head…”Did you remember to close that section?”.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thinking About Chalk</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/thinkingaboutchalk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/thinkingaboutchalk/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My grandfather was a high school history teacher. He had to write with chalk…Promethean boards didn’t exist. I don’t remember this personally because he had retired by the time I was a kid, but my mom used to tell me that his hands would get so dry from using the chalk that they would crack and bleed. Sometimes during class. So, here’s my grandfather, the kindest and most patient man I have ever met, bleeding in order to make it possible for his students to copy down notes and be better informed human beings.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I like to read cursive. Really. Which is convenient since I study early and antebellum southern history. Periods that produced a surprising amount of documents written in cursive. As a PhD student in the Digital History program at Clemson University I am privileged to be a research assistant with the real-life history project at Cemetery Hill. I have also had the opportunity to be involved with getting the Hidden History summer camps for middle and elementary school students started at Clemson hosted by the Cemetery Hill research project.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/portfolio/content/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/portfolio/content/</guid>
      <description>&lt;span class=&#34;section__title&#34;&gt;{{ .Title | default &#34;Projects&#34; }}&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;portfolio__content&#34;&gt;&#xA;    {{ range first 1 (where .Data.Pages &#34;Params.featured&#34; &#34;==&#34; true) }}&#xA;        &lt;section class=&#34;portfolio__featured-project&#34;&gt;&#xA;            &lt;div class=&#34;section-inner&#34;&gt;&#xA;                &lt;div class=&#34;portfolio_content&#34;&gt;&#xA;                    &lt;div class=&#34;item featured text-center&#34;&gt;&#xA;                        &lt;span class=&#34;project__title&#34;&gt;&#xA;                            &lt;a href=&#34;{{ .Params.Link }}&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;{{ .Title }}&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;                        &lt;/span&gt;&#xA;                        &lt;p class=&#34;project__subtitle-big&#34;&gt;&#xA;                            &lt;sup&gt;&lt;i class=&#34;fa fa-quote-left&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&#xA;                            {{ .Params.description }}&#xA;                            &lt;sup&gt;&lt;i class=&#34;fa fa-quote-right&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&#xA;                        &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;                        &lt;div class=&#34;project__featured-image&#34;&gt;&#xA;                            {{ if .Params.screenshot }}&#xA;                                &lt;img src=&#34;{{ .Params.screenshot }}&#34;  alt=&#34;{{ .Title }}&#34;&gt;&#xA;                            {{ end }}&#xA;                        &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;                        &lt;div class=&#34;project__summary&#34;&gt;&#xA;                                {{ .Content }}&#xA;                        &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;                    &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;                &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;            &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/section&gt;&#xA;    {{ end }}&#xA;    &lt;section&gt;&#xA;        &lt;div class=&#34;portfolio_content&#34;&gt;&#xA;            &lt;hr class=&#34;divider&#34;&gt;&#xA;            {{ range (where .Data.Pages &#34;Params.featured&#34; &#34;!=&#34; true).ByDate.Reverse }}&#xA;            &lt;div class=&#34;row&#34;&gt;&#xA;                &lt;div class=&#34;col-md-4 col-sm-4 col-xs-12&#34; href=&#34;{{ .Params.link }}&#34;&#xA;                    target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;&#xA;                    {{ if .Params.screenshot }}&#xA;                        &lt;img class=&#34;project__image img-responsive&#34; src=&#34;{{ .Params.screenshot }}&#34; alt=&#34;{{ .Title }}&#34;&gt;&#xA;                    {{ end }}&#xA;                &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;                &lt;div class=&#34;col-md-8 col-sm-8 col-xs-12&#34;&gt;&#xA;                    &lt;span class=&#34;project__title&#34;&gt;&#xA;                        &lt;a href=&#34;{{ .Params.link }}&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;{{ .Title }}&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;                    &lt;/span&gt;&#xA;                    &lt;span class=&#34;project__subtitle-small&#34;&gt;&#xA;                        &lt;sup&gt;&lt;i class=&#34;fa fa-quote-left&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&#xA;                        {{ .Params.description }}&#xA;                        &lt;sup&gt;&lt;i class=&#34;fa fa-quote-right&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&#xA;                    &lt;/span&gt;&#xA;                    &lt;span class=&#34;project__summary&#34;&gt;&#xA;                        {{ .Content }}&#xA;                    &lt;/span&gt;&#xA;                &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;            &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;            &lt;div class=&#34;row-space&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;            {{ end }}&#xA;        &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/cv/</guid>
      <description>&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
